Indiana University President's Office records, 1962-1968 C304
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1962-1968
  - Indiana (Box 84)
    - Vendors conflict of interest, 1966 (Box 96)
    - Vocational technical college, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 96)
  - Indianapolis (Box 96)
    - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 96)
    - Campus development, 1965-1966 (Box 96)
    - Community, Special committee to study education needs in, 1962-1963 (Box 96)
    - Council on world affairs, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 96)
    - District dental society, 1965 (Box 96)
    - Hebrew congregation, 1967 (Box 96)
    - Hospital development association, 1962-1967 (Box 96)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 96)
    - Motor speed way, 1967 (Box 96)
    - News (Box 96)
      - News, Star, and Times, 1965-1966 (Box 96)
      - Star, articles by Harrison J. Ullmann, 1964-1965 (Box 96)
      - News, Star, and Times, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 96)
      - Newspapers, correspondence on articles regarding four state schools budget requests, 1962-1963 (Box 96)
      - Other sources. State-supported University controversy, 1962-1963 (Box 97)
      - News, Star, and Times, 1963-1964 (Box 97)
    - Symphony Orchestra, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 97)
    - Urban League, 1966 (Box 97)
  - Indonesia (Box 97)
    - A.I.D. Contract, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 97)
    - International Cooperation Administration Contract, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 97)
  - Institutes (Box 97)
    - For teachers of high-school biology, 1964 (Box 97)
    - Annual institute on hospital accounting and finance, 1962-1963 (Box 97)
    - A-Z, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 97)
    - Of international education, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 97)
    - Of Psychiatric research, 1959-1964; (2 folders) (Box 97)
    - Proposal for Reading Research institute, 1965 (Box 97)
    - Of Public adiminstration, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 97)
    - For services to education, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 98)
    - For sex research, 1962-1968 (Box 98)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 98)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 98)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 98)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 98)
      - Annual Report, 1966-67 (Box 98)
    - Of urban studies, 1966 (Box 98)
    - Of World literature, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - Insurance (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 98)
    - Big Ten Bus. Officers survey of liability of educational institutions, 1966 (Box 98)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1965; (6 folders) (Box 98)
    - Life insurance study sponsored by Consumers Union, 1963 (Box 98)
    - Group insurance (Box 98)
      - Memos re: Participation, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 98)
  - Intensive language training center, 1963-1970; (3 folders) (Box 98)
  - Inter, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 98)
  - Intercollegiate (Box 98)
    - Athletics, department of, Annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 98)
    - Conference, 1965-1968; (4 folders) (Box 98)
    - Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 99)
      - Minutes of meeting of athletic directors, 1962 (Box 99)
      - Minutes of meeting of joint group, no date (Box 99)
      - Minutes of meeting of athletic directors and faculty representatives, 1963-1964 (Box 99)
      - Minutes of meeting of joint group, 1963-1964 (Box 99)
  - Interdisciplinary conference on paralanguage and kinesics, 1962 (Box 99)
  - Internal auditing (Box 99)
    - 1962-1968, (8 folders) (Box 99)
    - Annual report, 1967-1968; 1963-1964 (Box 99)
  - International activities at Indiana University (Box 99)
    - Survey of, 1966-1968 (Box 99)
    - Louisville Courier Journal, 1966 (Box 99)
    - Newsletter, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - International affairs center, 1965-1966 (Box 99)
  - International affairs center (Box 100)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 100)
    - Strengthening international studies at Indiana University: Next five years, 1965 (Box 100)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 100)
  - International biological station, 1965 (Box 100)
  - International Business Machines [I.B.M.] (Box 100)
    - 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 100)
    - Correspondence, no date (Box 100)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 100)
    - Executive review of data processing, 1966 (Box 100)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 100)
  - International development (Box 100)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 100)
    - Research center annual report, 1963-1965; (2 folders) (Box 100)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 100)
    - Advisory board meeting (Box 100)
      - April 29, 1968 (Box 100)
      - April 1, 1968 (Box 100)
      - February 28, 1968 (Box 100)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 100)
  - International education act (Box 100)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 100)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 100)
  - International grants committee, 1966-1967 (Box 100)
  - International week (Box 100)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 100)
    - Opening panel discussion, 1965 (Box 100)
  - Inter-university committee on travel grants (Box 101)
    - 1962-1968, (6 folders) (Box 101)
    - Policy meeting, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 101)
  - Inventory department, annual report, 1963-1964; 1967-1968 (Box 101)
  - Investments (Box 101)
    - Sinking fund and operating statements, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 101)
    - Report, 1967-1968; (5 folders) (Box 101)
    - Committee of the board of trustees and investments (Box 101)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 101)
      - Meeting, November 12, 1966; (3 folders) (Box 101)
      - Meeting, October 14, 1966 (Box 101)
    - Report, [1966] (Box 101)
    - Committee agenda, 1966; (2 folders) (Box 102)
    - Committee of the board of trustees and investments (Box 102)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 102)
  - Invitations list, Elvis Stahr, 1964-1965 (Box 102)
  - Iowa, University of, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - I, 1962-1963 (Box 102)
  - Ir, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - J, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - Jaco, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - Jam, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - Japan, 1966-1968 (Box 102)
  - Je, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - Jens, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - Jewish Chautauqua Society, 1966-1968 (Box 102)
  - Jo, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - Job corps training center (Box 102)
    - 1964-1968, (2 folders) (Box 102)
    - Policy committee, 1965-1966 (Box 102)
  - John Herron Art museum, 1956-1968; (4 folders) (Box 102)
  - Johnson, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - Johnson, Johnson, and Roy, 1963-1967 (Box 102)
  - Jol, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - Jor, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 102)
  - Jordan, James R., 1962-1965 (Box 103)
  - Journal of American History (formerly Mississippi Valley Historical Review), 1964-1968; (2 folders) (Box 103)
  - Journal of Mathematics & Mechanics – Financial Report, 1966-1967 (Box 103)
  - Journalism, Department of (Box 103)
    - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 103)
    - Foreign Journalist Project, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 103)
  - Ju, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 103)
  - Junior Division (Box 103)
    - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 103)
    - Annual Reports, 1962-1967; (4 folders) (Box 103)
  - K, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 103)
  - Kal, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 103)
  - Kansas, University of, 1966-1968 (Box 103)
  - Kansas, University of, and Kansas State University, 1962-1965 (Box 103)
  - Kap, 1962-1968 (Box 103)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi & Tau Beta Sigma, National Convention, 1965 (Box 103)
  - Kas, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 103)
  - Kastner, H. (Harold), 1963-1965 (Box 103)
  - Ke, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 103)
  - Kel, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 103)
  - Keller, K.T., 1964-1965 (Box 103)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1965 (Box 103)
  - Ken (Box 104)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 104)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 104)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 104)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 104)
  - Kennan, George F., 1963 (Box 104)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1967-1968 (Box 104)
  - Kentucky, University of, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 104)
  - Kenyatta, Jane, 1968 (Box 104)
  - Kenyatta, Jane, March 1968 (Box 104)
  - Ker, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 104)
  - Ki, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 104)
  - Kimble, George H.T., 1962-1966 (Box 104)
  - Kin, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 104)
  - King, Martin Luther – Memorial Service, 1968 (Box 104)
  - Kir, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 104)
  - Kl, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Kli, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Klinge, Paul, 1962-1968 (Box 104)
  - Kn, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 104)
  - Ko, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 104)
  - Koh, 1964-1966; (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Kor, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 104)
  - Korea Project – A.I.D. Contract in Nursing Education, 1962-1966 (Box 104)
  - Kr, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 104)
  - Krannert, Herman C., 1965-1968 (Box 104)
  - Kre, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Kro, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Ku, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 104)
  - Kul, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - L, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 104)
  - Labor Education and Research Center, Annual Reports, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 105)
  - Labor Relations; Labor Unions, 1967 (Box 105)
  - Lak, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 105)
  - The Lake County Medical Society Dinner honoring Dr. E.S. "Jack" Jones, 1966 (Box 105)
  - Lan, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 105)
  - Lane Bryant Awards, 1966-1968 (Box 105)
  - Lang, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Language Laboratory, 1964-1965 (Box 105)
  - [Intensive] Language Training Center (Box 105)
    - Electronics, 1963-1964 (Box 105)
    - Honorariums, 1962-1963 (Box 105)
  - Lar, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Las, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Latin American Music Center, Annual Report, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Latin American Program, 1961-1968; (5 folders) (Box 105)
  - Laves, Walter H.C., 1962-1965 (Box 105)
  - Law, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 105)
  - Law School (Box 105)
    - Bloomington, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 105)
    - Bloomington and Indianapolis, Annual Report, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 105)
    - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 105)
    - Dean Leon H. Wallace, 1964-1966 (Box 106)
    - Dean, Applicants and Candidates, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 106)
    - Fund, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 106)
    - Indiana Continuing Legal Education Forum, 1963-1966; (3 folders) (Box 106)
    - Indianapolis Division, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 106)
    - Report of Visit by Willard R. Pedrick and Benjamin F. Boyer, 1964 (Box 106)
    - Visiting Committee, 1964-1966; (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Le, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 106)
  - League of Women Voters, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Learning Resources Institute, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Lee, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 106)
  - Legal Counsel, Litigation, Liability Policy, 1963-1968 (Box 106)
  - Legislature, 1963; (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Legislators – Alumni Meetings, 1966 (Box 107)
  - Leh, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 107)
  - Len, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 107)
  - Letters, School of, Annual Report, 1963-1964 (Box 107)
  - Lev, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 107)
  - Lew, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 107)
  - Lewis, John P., 1962-1966 (Box 107)
  - Li, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 107)
  - Library (Box 107)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 107)
    - University Libraries, Annual Report, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 107)
    - Use of Facilities by other Universities and Colleges, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Library School, 1966-1968 (Box 107)
  - Library Science, Division of, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Lilly, Eli, 1964 (Box 107)
  - Lilly Library (Box 107)
    - 1962-1968, (6 folders) (Box 107)
    - Advisory Committee Annual Report, 1962-1963 (Box 107)
    - Rare Book Acquisitions Report, 1961-1963; (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Lin, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 107)
  - Linguistics, Department of, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 107)
  - Linguistics, Preliminary Final Report on a Multiple-Credit Self-Instructional Elementary French Course, 1965 (Box 108)
  - Linguistics Institute (Box 108)
    - General, 1964 (Box 108)
    - Final Report, 1964 (Box 108)
  - Lininger, Lloyd L., 1964 (Box 108)
  - Link Observatory, 1967-1968 (Box 108)
  - List of Special Folders in General File, 1966 (Box 108)
  - Lit, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 108)
  - Lo, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 108)
  - Lockefield Gardens (Indianapolis) (Box 108)
  - Log of correspondence/appointments, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Lon, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 108)
  - Loonsten, Fritz (Box 108)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 108)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 108)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 108)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 108)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 108)
  - Lot, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Lu, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 108)
  - Lun, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 108)
  - Ly, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 108)
  - M, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 108)
  - Mac, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 108)
  - Mack, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 108)
  - Mad, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 109)
  - Mah, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 109)
  - Mail Service (Box 109)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 109)
    - Annual Report, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 109)
  - Special Mailings, 1966-1968 (Box 109)
  - Mailings (Box 109)
    - General, 1965-1966 (Box 109)
    - Freshman Convocation and Lake Co. Med. Society, 1966 (Box 109)
    - State of the University, 1966 (Box 109)
    - Student Senate Speech, 1965 (Box 109)
    - Barbecue & Charge to Class, 1965 (Box 109)
    - Red Mass and Founder's Day Speeches, 1965 (Box 109)
    - Publishers, Radio and TV, 1965 (Box 109)
    - Phi Beta Kappans, 1965 (Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous, Feb. 13-16, 1965 (Box 109)
    - Copy of Speech by Pres. Wescoe, 1965 (Box 109)
    - To Publishers, 5 enclosures, 1964 (Box 109)
    - Kling Speech, CIC comments, 1964 (Box 109)
    - Special Mailings, 1966-1968 (Box 109)
  - Mal, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 109)
  - Mali – A.I.D. Contract and Training Program, 1962 (Box 109)
  - Man, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 109)
  - Manchester College Commencement, 1965 (Box 109)
  - Manpower, 1966-1968 (Box 109)
  - Maps, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 109)
  - Mar, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 109)
  - Mark, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 109)
  - Mart, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 109)
  - Mas, 1962-1968 (Box 110)
  - Mass Communications, 1965-1966 (Box 110)
  - Mass Communications, Annual Report, 1963-1964 (Box 110)
  - Mat, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - Materials Store and Salvage, Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 110)
  - Mathematics, Department of, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - Mathematics, Department of, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - Matt, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - May, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 110)
  - McA, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - McC, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - McCo, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 110)
  - McD, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - McDermott, Russell W., 1963 (Box 110)
  - McE, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - McG, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - McGr, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - McI, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - McK, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - McKinney, Frank E., 1966 (Box 110)
  - McL, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 110)
  - McN, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - Me, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - Combined Degree in Medicine, 1957-1962 (Box 110)
  - Medicine, School of (Box 110)
    - Proposals for the establishment of a 2nd State Medical School in Indiana, 1965-1967 (Box 110)
    - Alumni Association, 1966 (Box 110)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 110)
    - Hospitals, 1966-1968 (Box 110)
    - Statistics, 1962-1963 (Box 110)
    - Planning Committee, 1963 (Box 110)
    - General (Box 111)
      - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 111)
    - Annual Report, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 111)
    - Future Medical Education in Indiana – "The Indiana Plan", 1966 (Box 111)
    - Alumni Association Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 111)
    - Alumni Day, 1968 (Box 111)
    - Biochemistry, 1963-1964 (Box 111)
  - Medical Center (Box 111)
    - Annual Report, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 111)
    - Capital Repair and Rehabilitation Projects, 1967-1969 (Box 111)
    - Foreign Student – Guilherme Mabunda, 1963 (Box 111)
    - Halls of Residence, 1964-1965 (Box 111)
    - Hospitals, 1962-1963 (Box 111)
    - News Bureau, 1966 (Box 111)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1966 (Box 111)
  - Medical Education (Box 111)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 111)
    - 1965-1966, (3 folders) (Box 111)
    - 1966-1973 (Box 111)
    - 1965-1966, (2 folders and some loose reports) (Box 112)
    - Controversy, 1965-1966 (Box 112)
    - Program, Conference notes, 1967 (Box 112)
  - Medical School at Ball State, Proposal for, 1964-1965 (Box 112)
  - Mei, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 112)
  - Menke, Robert H. (), 1966-1968 (Box 112)
  - Mental Retardation Program, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 112)
  - Mer, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 112)
  - Mes, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 112)
  - Metaphysical Society of America, 1965 (Box 112)
  - Methodist Church, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 112)
  - Metropolitan Opera, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 112)
  - Metz, Arthur R., Foundation, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 112)
  - Mey, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 112)
  - Mi, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 112)
  - Michigan State University, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 112)
  - Michigan, University of, Ann Arbor (Box 113)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 113)
    - Sesquicentennial celebration, 1967 (Box 113)
  - Mid, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 113)
  - Midwest interlibrary corporation (Box 113)
    - 1962-1965, (4 folders) (Box 113)
    - Newsletter, 1962-1963 (Box 113)
  - Midwest program of airborne television instruction, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 113)
  - Midwest seminar on U.S. foreign policy, Wingspread (Box 113)
    - 1965-1969, (6 folders) (Box 113)
  - Midwest universities consortium for international activities (Box 114)
    - Exhibits and appendices to the final report, undated (Box 114)
    - 1962-1965, (3 folders) (Box 114)
  - Mil, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 114)
  - Military department, annual report, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 114)
  - Mill, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 114)
  - Milli, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 114)
  - Minnesota, University of, Minneapolis, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 114)
  - Minton, 1966 (Box 114)
  - Misra, Chandra, 1964 (Box 114)
  - Mississippi Valley historical association and review, 1962 (Box 114)
  - Missouri, University of, Columbia and Rolla, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 114)
  - Mit, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 114)
  - Mo, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 114)
  - Modern Dance Workshop, Indiana University, undated (Box 114)
  - Moh, 1962-1968; (undated) (Box 114)
  - Mon, 1962-1968; (undated) (Box 114)
  - Monroe county (Box 114)
    - 1964-1968, (3 folders) (Box 114)
    - County airport, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 114)
  - Monroe reservoir (Box 114)
    - 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 114)
    - Research station director and land acquisition, 1965-1966 (Box 114)
  - Monroe reservoir (Box 115)
    - 1962-1966, (4 folders) (Box 115)
    - Proposed band camp, 1965-1966 (Box 115)
  - Moo, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 115)
  - Mor, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 115)
  - Morr, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 115)
  - Morrow, William, 1963 (Box 115)
  - Mos, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 115)
  - Mu, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 115)
  - Musical arts center proposals, 1967-1968 (Box 115)
  - Muhler, Joseph C., 1966-1968 (Box 115)
  - Mul, 1962-1968 (Box 115)
  - Muller, H.J., 1963-1968 (Box 115)
  - Mur, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 115)
  - Museum of anthropology, history and folklore, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 115)
  - Music (Box 115)
    - American Woodwind quintet, 1964-1965 (Box 115)
    - School of (Box 115)
      - 1962-1968, (7 folders) (Box 115)
      - Ballet, 1966-1968 (Box 115)
      - 1966-1969, (2 folders) (Box 116)
      - Bands, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 116)
      - Baroque chamber players, 1966 (Box 116)
      - Beauxarts trio, 1962-1966 (Box 116)
      - Belles of Indiana, 1965 (Box 116)
      - Berkshire quartet, 1965-1966 (Box 116)
      - Calendar of events, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 116)
      - Concert fund, report on operations, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 116)
      - East hall, 1966-1968 (Box 116)
      - Jazz, 1965-1966 (Box 116)
      - Latin American music center, 1963-1968; (2 folders) (Box 116)
      - Library, 1966 (Box 116)
      - Musical organizations, operating statements, 1962-1967; (4 folders) (Box 116)
      - Opera theatre, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 116)
      - Orchestra, 1966-1968 (Box 116)
      - Parsifal, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 116)
      - Singing Hoosiers, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 116)
      - Woodwind quintet, 1962-1963 (Box 116)
  - Musical Arts Center, 1966-1968 (Box 116)
  - My, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 116)
  - N, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 116)
  - Narcotics, 1966-1968 (Box 116)
  - NASA, 1963-1964 (Box 116)
  - NASULGC meeting, Columbus, OH, November 13-15, 1967 (Box 116)
  - Nat, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 116)
  - National art center project feasibility study, 1966 (Box 116)
  - National Audubon society, 1963-1975 (Box 116)
  - National (Box 117)
    - Miscellaneous A-L, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 117)
    - Miscellaneous M-Z, 1962-1968 (Box 117)
  - National academy of sciences, 1966-1968 (Box 117)
  - National academy of science (Box 117)
    - Site evaluation visit, 1965-1966; (4 folders) (Box 117)
    - Testimonial dinner for Frederick Seitz, 1962 (Box 117)
  - National Aeronautics Space Administration, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 117)
  - National Art Center Project, 1966 (Box 117)
  - National beta club, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 118)
  - National center for school and college television (Box 118)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 118)
    - Annual report, 1967-1968 (Box 118)
  - National committee for the Florence agreement, 1962 (Box 118)
  - National council of the churches of Christ in the U.S.A., 1966-1968 (Box 118)
  - National defense education act of 1958 (Box 118)
    - 1962-1968, (6 folders) (Box 118)
    - Application for title IV, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with legislators, 1964; 1966; (2 folders) (Box 118)
    - Modern language fellowships, 1965 (Box 118)
    - Language institute, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 118)
  - National defense language institute, 1963-1964 (Box 119)
  - National educational television film service (Box 119)
    - Annual report, 1964-1968; (8 folders) (Box 119)
    - Radio center, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 119)
  - National education improvement act of 1963 (Box 119)
  - National environmental health center, 1964-1965 (Box 119)
  - National foundation on the arts and the humanities and national endowment for the humanities, 1966-1968 (Box 119)
  - National industrial conference board, 1965-1966 (Box 119)
  - National instructional television library, 1964-1965 (Box 119)
  - National inter-fraternity council, Pittsburgh Hilton Hotel, 192 (Box 119)
  - National medal of science, undated (Box 119)
  - National research council, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 119)
  - National science foundation, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 119)
  - National science foundation (Box 120)
    - 1962-1965, (3 folders) (Box 120)
    - Science advisory committee, 1964-1966; (3 folders) (Box 120)
    - Grants and proposals (Box 120)
      - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 120)
      - Centers of excellence proposals, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 120)
      - Grant for observatory for graduate research in astronomy and astrophysics, 1965 (Box 120)
    - Science development program in the physical sciences, 1965 (Box 120)
    - National medal of science, 1966 (Box 120)
    - Study of selected policies and practices associated with the administration of research activities of colleges and universities, 1963-1964 (Box 120)
    - Accelerator proposal (low energy), 1964-1966; (2 folders) (Box 120)
  - National teachers corps, 1966 (Box 120)
  - National technical institute for the deaf, 1965-1966 (Box 120)
  - Natural areas program (Box 120)